Guide to the Barbara Kopple Collection on the Peekskill Riots TAM.307
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Subject Files, Individuals
  - Drake, Peter (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Duncombe, Patricia (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Ellen, Milton (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Ellis, James R. (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Fanelli, George M. (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Feldman, Isidore (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Fenaughty, Michael (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Ficke, Richard (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Field, Robert J. (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Fiario, Samuel (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Flynt, Milton (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Fowler, Richard (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Fox, Samuel (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Gambino, Salvatore (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Gamsu, Gilbert (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Gell-man, Benedict (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Geotz, Theodore (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Gerlach, Herbert C. (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Gerst, Meyer (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Gilbert, Thomas L. (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Giosi, Michael (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Glasheen, Daniel (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Glieberman, David (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Gleisher, Norman (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Goldberg, Gustave (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Goldman, Henry (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Goldsand, Isidore (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Grant, Allen (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Ham, Gerald (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Harontourian, Richard (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Heady, John and Frank Cowa (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Heady, Robert (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Henson, Vincent (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Hergernhan, John C. (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Heiman, Harry G. (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Hersey, William (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Hess, Kurt (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Hoffman, Roslyn (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Hoffman, Leon (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Hollis, David (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Horn, Nora (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Horton, Robert (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Hoy, John E. (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Huber, John (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Hughes, John (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Hynes, James A. (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Ikeler, Donald F. (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Innes, Thomas (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Innis, Lorenzo (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Iozzo, Nicholas (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - McCarthy, Terrence (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Jacquier, Ives (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Johnson, Alvin (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Jamison, Willis
  - Jamison, Willis (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Kall, John J. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Kane, Herbert J. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Kaplan, Sidney (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Kaufman, Maurice (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Keisler, Lester (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Kelly, Walter (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy, Albert J. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Keys, Betty (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Kittner, Lillian (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Koppel, Ira (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Kornfedder, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Kramer, Aaron (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Kroner, Charles (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lafer, Laurence (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Lancaster, Nicholas (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Lapolla, Ray (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Lavazerro, Antonio (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Lemak, Frank (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Lenich, Anthony (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Lenich, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Lenich, Peter (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Lesser, Sy (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Levenson, Eugene (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Levy, Herbert M. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Lewis, Harold (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Lewis, Herbert L. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Lewis, Walter (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Lewis, William (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Licht, Fanny (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Litman, Milton (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Livingston, David (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Lopez, John (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Lucas, Paul (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Luznas, Anthony (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Lyden, Frank (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Madole, James H. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Mahan, Bernard, R. (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Mahler, Sarah (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Mahon, Harry (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Malkin, Maurice (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Malles, John (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Mallette, Frank R. (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Manopoli, John F. (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Manzonie, Archie (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Marcus, Sidney (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Mason, Sidney (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Matthews, J.B. (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - McCarthy, Florence (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - McCoy, Bill (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - McDonald, William P. (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - McDowell, Wilson (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - McGrath, Edward (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - McLaughlin, William (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Metzger, William (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Miller, David (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Mobile, Mary (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Moniz, Raymond T. (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Moore, Howard R. (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Moran, Walter J. (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Morris, Paul C. (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Morris, Robert (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Naylor, Edward L. (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Naylor, Frank (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Newton, John (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - O'neill, Thomas (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Orvis, Shuyler A. Jr. (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Oswald, Theodore (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Page, James K. (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Parker, Catherine (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Player, Mary (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Player, Maurice (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Powers, John P. (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Prince, Karl (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Quinn, Francis (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Rabinbach, Gabriel (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Reitman, Alan (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Renza, James (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Resnick, Ephraim (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Resnick, Rose (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Rick, Chester (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Roberts, Charles (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Rogan, Ambrose (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Rogers, Ralph (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Roland, Ted (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Rothenberg, Charles (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Rothstein, Harry (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Rubenfeld, Leonard (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Rubenfeld, Louis (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Ruscoe, Fred W. (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Russell, Edward H. (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Ryder, herbert (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Sayers, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Salti, Jean and Michael (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Scandlen, Edward T. (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Schiavone, Andrew (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Schultz, Benjamin (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Schuyler, George (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Schwiter, Herman (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Scott, Edmund (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Secor, Howard A. (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Secor, William (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Seitz, Helen and Jules (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Seligson, Charles (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Shapiro, Ralph (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Sharp, Parent (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Sharrow, Victor (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Shongut, A.L. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Slater, William (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Slutsky, Samuel L. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Frances (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Sniffen, Richard (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Sommers, Martin (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Sousa, Tony (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Spanko, John (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Spolansky, Jacob (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Steiner, Abraham (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Stevens, John (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Stewart, Martin (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Stokes, Alvin W. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Stout, Rex (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Stringer, Tolon Leroy (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Stuart, John J. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Szego, Stephen (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Tinsely, Wilbur (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Toborg, William J. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Tompkins, Richard (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Travis, Josiah H. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Utter, Gerard (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Varian, Robert (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Varnava, Frank (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Villegas, Josephine (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Walderman, Stanley (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Wallerstein, Seymour (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Walsh, John (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Webber, Simon (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Weeks, Frederick E. (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Weintraub, Carl (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - White, John W. (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Williams, Blanche (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Winogradski, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Woltman, Frederick (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Woods, Gene (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Yergan, Max (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Zackheim, Mary (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Zelman, Benjamin (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Zimmer, John (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Zitron, Abraham (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Series VI: Photographs, 1949
  Series VI includes negatives, contact sheets, photographic prints, and one scrapbook documenting the Peekskill riots and subsequent Paul Robseon concerts. Images depict the concert, Paul Robeson, protest parades, mob violence, police response, and the destruction of the park, cars, buses, and books. Most images are unidentified and come from a variety of sources, including newswire prints, police photographs, and original photographs taken by witnesses to the events.
  - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Photographic Prints, 1949 August-1949 September (Box 10, Box 11, Box 12)
  - Scrapbook, including photographic prints, newspaper clippings, memoranda, and ephemera documenting the concerts, riots, and police response, 1949 (Box 13)
- Series VII. 2014 Accession, 1949
  Arrangement
  These materials have not been arranged by an archivist; original order is unknown.
  - Grand Jury Materials, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Telegrams, 1949 September (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - District Attorney Report, 1949 September 6 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Printed Ephemera, circa 1949 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Civil Rights Congress Materials, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Police Reports and Transmissions, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 6)